http://www.webpage-teacher.com/privacy.htm

Privacy Policy Statement
This is a web site of Pinsoft Software.
Our postal address is 70 Bronzewing StTahmoor, NSW 2573, Australia.
We can be reached via e-mail by clicking this email link. Or you
can reach us by telephone at +61 2 46818818
Webpage-Teacher.com (Pinsoft Software in association with Leslie Pinczi) strives to
offer its visitors computer software that will benefit their online computer education, especially how to create
websites using the HTML computer language. We may use
Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number)
subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address
to any unauthorized third party. Period.
How we gather information from users
How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities
in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to
provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain
features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. You may provide information when you
participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas
of our site. Like most Web sites, Webpage-Teacher.com (Pinsoft Software in association with Leslie Pinczi)
also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent
to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology
to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user
name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control
the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional
technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to
provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do
you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password,
and we may not be able to customize the site's features according to your preferences.
Webpage-Teacher.com (Pinsoft Software in association with Leslie Pinczi) does not recommend or endorse any specific
advertising or marketing strategy. We recommend that you research all advertising and marketing strategy thoroughly.
What we do with the information we collect
Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content
and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone.
Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example,
we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance
our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated
Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not
include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually.
We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on www.webpage-teacher.com to communicate with you about your
registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by www.webpage-teacher.com
and other topics we think you might find of interest.
Personally Identifiable Information collected by Webpage-Teacher.com (Pinsoft Software in association with Leslie Pinczi) may also
be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions,
administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support
for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your information only
as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with
other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your
information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with
the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please
note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.
Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements
Webpage-Teacher.com (Pinsoft Software in association with Leslie Pinczi) expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the
privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers
accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our
site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a www.webpage-teacher.com page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a
third party. Also, through Webpage-Teacher.com (Pinsoft Software in association with Leslie Pinczi) you may be introduced to, or be able to
access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. Webpage-Teacher.com (Pinsoft Software in association with Leslie Pinczi)
is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties
when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.
While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify
some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include
cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site
may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. Webpage-Teacher.com (Pinsoft Software in association with Leslie Pinczi)
does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of
such third parties.
You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information
can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals
or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Webpage-Teacher.com (Pinsoft Software in association with Leslie Pinczi) and this policy.
Children
Webpage-Teacher.com (Pinsoft Software in association with Leslie Pinczi) does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or
about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy,
we will delete that information immediately. If you believe Webpage-teacher.com (Pinsoft Software. in association with Leslie Pinczi) has any information from
or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the address listed above.
Changes to this Policy
Webpage-Teacher.com (Pinsoft Software in association with Leslie Pinczi) reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically
for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to
the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.
Governing law
This policy and the use of this Site are governed by NSW law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a
mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Sydney, Australia. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be
shared equally by each of us.
If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following
location: Sydney, Australia, under the rules of the Australian Arbitration Association. Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court
with jurisdiction to do so.
Webpage-teacher.com is controlled, operated and administered entirely within Webpage-Teacher.com (Pinsoft Software in association with Leslie Pinczi). This statement and the
policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
How To Make A Web Page
How To Build A Web Page in Only 60 Minutes
Learn Basic HTML Code FAST!
FREE Web Page HTML Tips
Earn $6.71 per sale with our Affiliate Program (Huge 75% Commission!) - Join Free Today!
